<Publish>
  <ModId Value="135367" />
	<DisplayName Value="Audio Switcher" />
	<ShortDescription Value="Switch siren, vehicle engine, and ambient sounds with custom WAV/OGG files." />
	<LongDescription>
    Audio Switcher lets you replace siren, vehicle engine, and ambient sounds with custom WAV/OGG files and allows for custom public transport announcements for transport lines.

    Supports local audio and modules.

    * All-in-one audio overhaul: customize Sirens, Vehicle Engines, Ambient Sounds, and Public Transport announcements in one mod.
    * Clean, centralized options UI: organized tabs and status panels make setup and troubleshooting straightforward.
    * Per-category defaults + precision overrides: set broad defaults, then override specific vehicles, ambient targets, and transit lines.
    * Per-line transit announcements: assign distinct arrival/departure audio per discovered line for more realistic network audio.
    * Smart scanning tools: rescan custom audio folders and in-game prefabs/targets/lines to keep options synced to your city.
    * Advanced audio profile editor: tune volume, pitch, spatial blend, doppler, spread, min/max distance, loop, rolloff, random start, and fade timings.
    * Instant preview workflow: audition selected sounds before committing changes.
    * Reliable fallback behavior: define what happens when a selected file is missing, including alternate sound choices.
    * City Sound Sets system: create, activate, rename, duplicate, update, and delete full sound presets.
    * City-based automation: bind sound sets to cities and auto-apply the right set when loading each city.
    * Built-in diagnostics: live scan statuses, validation reports, and debug reporting help catch setup issues quickly.
    * Developer runtime audio tools: inspect and preview detected in-game sound sources with read-only SFX parameter visibility.
    * Module packaging workflow: build reusable audio modules from selected local assets.
    * PDX asset publishing pipeline: build-and-upload modules with visibility control, create/update modes, description, thumbnail selection, preflight checks, and dependency handling.
    * Safety-focused publishing UX: confirmation prompts, in-progress safeguards, and clear build/upload status feedback throughout.

    CHECK OUT:

    * New Improved Aircraft Sounds: https://mods.paradoxplaza.com/mods/139345/Any
    * LA/NY Siren Pack: https://mods.paradoxplaza.com/mods/139340/Any

    Known issues:
    * Sound set may not always apply correctly if a save is renamed.
    * Changing some vehicles assigned to transport line may lead to dead prefab.
  </LongDescription>
	<Thumbnail Value="Images/Audio Switcher Logo.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Images/Screen_Gen.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Images/Screen_PT.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Images/Screen_Siren.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Images/Screen_Siren2.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Images/Screen_Engine.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Images/Screen_Ambient.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Images/Screen_Prof.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Images/Screen_Dev.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Images/Screen_Dev2.jpg" />
  <Screenshot Value="Images/Screen_Dev3.jpg" />
  <!--CHANGE LOG-->
	<ChangeLog Value="Fixed broken UI images, Fixed 'don't show again', Major performance pass" />
  <Tag Value="" />
  <!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
  <ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/audio-switcher.1903848/" />
  <!--Version of the mod-->
  <ModVersion Value="2.5.2" />
  <!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
  <GameVersion Value="1.5.6f1" />
  <!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
  <Dependency Id="" />
  <!--Required DLC, can be set multiple times. Supported values are "Landmark Buildings", "San Fransisco Set", "Beach Properties", "Urban Promenades", "Modern Architecture"-->
  <RequiredDLC Value="" />
  <!--External link, can be set multiple times. supported types are "discord", "github", "youtube", "twitch", "x", "paypal", "patreon", "buymeacoffee", "kofi", "crowdin", "gitlab", "gofundme"-->
  <ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/SNIT01/CS2-Audio-Switcher" />
  <!--Supported values Public, Private, Unlisted-->
  <AccessLevel Value="Public" />
</Publish>
                                              